<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>nullium</title><link href="http://nullium.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://nullium.com/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://nullium.com/</id><updated>2013-09-25T09:00:00+08:00</updated><entry><title>Nice Simple Battery 1.6.0 Released</title><link href="http://nullium.com/blog/nicesimplebattery-1.6.0-released/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-09-25T09:00:00+08:00</updated><author><name>null</name></author><id>tag:nullium.com,2013-09-25:blog/nicesimplebattery-1.6.0-released/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Nice Simple Battery has been updated to 1.6.0. Now you can draw the small battery cap on top of your battery icon. It looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="nullium-blog-post-image-center" href="../../static/images/blog/nicesimplebattery-1.6.0-released-1.png"&gt;&lt;img src="../../static/images/blog/nicesimplebattery-1.6.0-released-1.png" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, there is a new option that allows you to use a different color to draw your battery icon when the battery power level is below a specified level. This should be useful to remind yourself to charge your battery when the battery is running low.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope you would like these new feature in this update. Here is the changelog:
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Version 1.6.0:  &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
- New feature: Option to draw the battery cap (under the "Battery Icon" section)&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Options for using a different color when battery is low (under the "Advanced Settings" section)&lt;br /&gt;
- Now clicking on the preview can change the power level displayed in the preview&lt;br /&gt;
- Applied a number of bug fixes and minor changes  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><category term="nice simple battery"></category></entry><entry><title>Nice Simple Clock 1.8.0 Released</title><link href="http://nullium.com/blog/nicesimpleclock-1.8.0-released/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-09-07T11:00:00+08:00</updated><author><name>null</name></author><id>tag:nullium.com,2013-09-07:blog/nicesimpleclock-1.8.0-released/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This week, I have updated the Nice Simple Clock. The new "year offset" feature is for special calendar systems that are being used in certain places around the world. Also, if you would like to see 13 instead 2013 for the year display, you can also subtract 2000 from the year using this new option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, I have added a few new time formats and new date separators in this update.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the changelog:
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Version 1.8.0:  &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
- New feature: Custom year offset option for special calendar systems (under "Other Settings")&lt;br /&gt;
- Added 3 new time formats and 3 new date separators&lt;br /&gt;
- Applied a number of bug fixes and minor changes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><category term="nice simple clock"></category></entry><entry><title>Nice Simple Photo Widget 1.3.0 Released</title><link href="http://nullium.com/blog/nicesimplephotowidget-1.3.0-released/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-09-01T01:00:00+08:00</updated><author><name>null</name></author><id>tag:nullium.com,2013-09-01:blog/nicesimplephotowidget-1.3.0-released/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Nice Simple Photo Widget 1.3.0 has been released. This update fixes a major problem where some photos do not fill the whole widget properly on some devices. It also includes a new frame size as well as an option requested by a number of users - the option to open the configuration window with double-clicks instead of single-clicks. This option actually already exists in Nice Simple Clock, and it has been proven quite useful to prevent the configuration window from being launched by accidental clicks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the changelog:
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Version 1.3.0:  &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
- Major fix: Photos are now always auto-scaled to be as large as possible within the widget&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Added the minimal frame size&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Now you can choose to open the widget configuration with double-clicks only (new option under "Other Settings")&lt;br /&gt;
- Some other minor improvements and changes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the way, I have made a &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xXAWx7gsJ-o"&gt;demonstration video&lt;/a&gt; to illustrate how to add a widget to your Android homescreen/desktop. The instruction is applicable to Android 4.0 or higher. I hope new widget users would find it useful as they ask me how to do it from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="nice simple photo widget"></category></entry><entry><title>StyleNote 2.0 Released</title><link href="http://nullium.com/blog/stylenote-2.0-released/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-08-25T23:00:00+08:00</updated><author><name>null</name></author><id>tag:nullium.com,2013-08-25:blog/stylenote-2.0-released/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;StyleNote 2.0 has been released!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a major update, there are many new features and improvements. The main interface has also been redesigned.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="nullium-blog-post-image-120" href="../../static/images/stylenote/ss1.png"&gt;&lt;img src="../../static/images/stylenote/ss1.png" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class="nullium-blog-post-image-120" href="../../static/images/stylenote/ss2.png"&gt;&lt;img src="../../static/images/stylenote/ss2.png" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class="nullium-blog-post-image-120" href="../../static/images/stylenote/ss3.png"&gt;&lt;img src="../../static/images/stylenote/ss3.png" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class="nullium-blog-post-image-120" href="../../static/images/stylenote/ss4.png"&gt;&lt;img src="../../static/images/stylenote/ss4.png" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class="nullium-blog-post-image-120" href="../../static/images/stylenote/ss5.png"&gt;&lt;img src="../../static/images/stylenote/ss5.png" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Better backup options, note search function, bullet point support, style templates, and dropbox cloud storage support are the key additions in this update. I am too tired right now to describe the new features one by one, but at the end of this blog post you can find the complete changelog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current users may check out the new instructions in the settings screen to learn about the new bullet point support. The settings screen can now be accessed from the main menu which can be opened via the 3-dots icon at the top-right corner of the app. Other new features are (hopefully) pretty straightforward to use. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you encounter any problem, please let me know. You may also check out the FAQ and ask questions in our &lt;a href="http://forums.nullium.com/index.php?topic=3.0"&gt;user forums&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy! :)
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Version 2.0.0:  &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
- New feature: Custom-scope note searching&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Notes &amp;amp; settings upload/download to/from your own Dropbox account for cloud backup or note sync among different devices&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Notes &amp;amp; settings export to HTML files which can be directly viewed on any computer&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Notes &amp;amp; settings import from exported HTML files&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Option to encrypt the exported files as .snb2 encrypted backup files&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Regular auto-backup to your SD card (Pro users can use Dropbox for auto-backup and customize the frequency)&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Bullet point list support which inserts bullet points automatically&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Bullet point cross-out button that can cross out the whole line of a bullet point with one click&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Style Templates for saving/loading your note color and size customization&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Widget option for center-aligning the note text on a widget&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Now you can specify a set of secret question and answer for password resetting in the future&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Now you can click on URLs (links) on the note list and launch the web browser&lt;br /&gt;
- New feature: Now you can send/share text to StyleNote from other programs&lt;br /&gt;
- Redesigned the main interface&lt;br /&gt;
- Many other improvements and minor changes&lt;br /&gt;
- StyleNote now requires Android 2.1 or newer (Android 1.5 and 1.6 can still use StyleNote 1.6.3 which can be downloaded from nullium.com)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><category term="stylenote"></category></entry><entry><title>New Website Launched</title><link href="http://nullium.com/blog/new-website-launched/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-08-18T00:00:00+08:00</updated><author><name>null</name></author><id>tag:nullium.com,2013-08-18:blog/new-website-launched/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have been working on this new website for a while so I am very excited to release it at last.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The blog part of this website is now hosted on &lt;a href="http://pages.github.com/"&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt; while the &lt;a href="http://forums.nullium.com"&gt;forums&lt;/a&gt; are hosted on my own Linux web server. Having my own web server also means that I will be able to create stuff that requires a server, which wasn't possible before. We shall see. For more technical details on what are used to build this new website, you may check out the updated &lt;a href="http://nullium.com/about/"&gt;about&lt;/a&gt; section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I have experiences in general computer usage and coding different kinds of software, I am pretty new to website development and Linux server management, so I really learned a lot during the process. I am quite happy with what I gained tho it was hard work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The overall design is finished, but parts of the website are still under construction. In particular I plan to create individual pages for some of my apps in the &lt;a href="http://nullium.com/creations/"&gt;creations&lt;/a&gt; section. I shall work on them later after I update the corresponding apps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Checking my old blog, I found that I haven't published anything in the last several months. I can easily list many excuses, like day job being more demanding, myself being burned out, not having enough spare time, and so on. However, honestly, the main reason is simply me not being good enough - I was not good enough to manage my time and myself. I am determined to improve and try to be productive again. I will try my best to update here more frequently and this blog will be a platform for me to track and publish my own progress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, besides the new website, I have also been working on StyleNote 2.0 lately. I will probably release it within the next few days if things go as planned. So, stay tuned. :)&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="website"></category></entry></feed>